iwantanewgirlfriend.com 2004-12-04

# :: I Want a New Girlfriend

**Visit These Great Sites**  
---  
  
| **Site of the Moment:   [ **Speeds Babes**](http://www.iwantanewgirlfriend.com/traffic-out.asp?site_id=5963 "Speeds Babes")  **  
---  
#1| [Girls Kissing Girls](http://www.iwantanewgirlfriend.com/traffic-out.asp?site_id=2643 "Girls Kissing Girls")| #8| [Drunk Girls Fuck](http://www.iwantanewgirlfriend.com/traffic-out.asp?site_id=6811 "Drunk Girls Fuck")| #15| [My Ex Girlfriend](http://www.iwantanewgirlfriend.com/traffic-out.asp?site_id=5413 "My Ex Girlfriend")  
#2| [Breakroom X Pussy](http://www.iwantanewgirlfriend.com/traffic-out.asp?site_id=3131 "Breakroom X Pussy")| #9| [Gallery Porn Post](http://www.iwantanewgirlfriend.com/traffic-out.asp?site_id=4660 "Gallery Porn Post")| #16| [Celebrity Factor](http://www.iwantanewgirlfriend.com/traffic-out.asp?site_id=6273 "Celebrity Factor")  
#3| [Revulsion.net](http://www.iwantanewgirlfriend.com/traffic-out.asp?site_id=2858 "Revulsion.net")| #10| [Hole in the .net](http://www.iwantanewgirlfriend.com/traffic-out.asp?site_id=3089 "Hole in the .net")| #17| [Texas Waterhole](http://www.iwantanewgirlfriend.com/traffic-out.asp?site_id=101 "Texas Waterhole")  
#4| [RickOnTV.com](http://www.iwantanewgirlfriend.com/traffic-out.asp?site_id=4974 "RickOnTV.com")| #11| [Los Blaugrana](http://www.iwantanewgirlfriend.com/traffic-out.asp?site_id=5682 "Los Blaugrana")| #18| [Paid Porn Surfers](http://www.iwantanewgirlfriend.com/traffic-out.asp?site_id=7670 "Paid Porn Surfers")  
#5| [College Sucks](http://www.iwantanewgirlfriend.com/traffic-out.asp?site_id=1159 "College Sucks")| #12| [Fuck A Cam Girl](http://www.iwantanewgirlfriend.com/traffic-out.asp?site_id=2553 "Fuck A Cam Girl")| #19| [PornHoolio.com](http://www.iwantanewgirlfriend.com/traffic-out.asp?site_id=4366 "PornHoolio.com")  
#6| [Dirty USA Nurse](http://www.iwantanewgirlfriend.com/traffic-out.asp?site_id=4423 "Dirty USA Nurse")| #13| [College Clam](http://www.iwantanewgirlfriend.com/traffic-out.asp?site_id=343 "College Clam")| #20| [Smit Happens](http://www.iwantanewgirlfriend.com/traffic-out.asp?site_id=3507 "Smit Happens")  
#7| [Porngasm](http://www.iwantanewgirlfriend.com/traffic-out.asp?site_id=3813 "Porngasm")| #14| [Teen Porno Pic](http://www.iwantanewgirlfriend.com/traffic-out.asp?site_id=7076 "Teen Porno Pic")| #21| [Ich Bin Hot (I am Hot)](http://www.iwantanewgirlfriend.com/traffic-out.asp?site_id=2648 "Ich Bin Hot \(I am Hot\)")  
  
* * *

Updates Every Ten Minutes - [Webmasters - Trade Traffic](http://www.iwantanewgirlfriend.com/traffic-webmasters.asp)  
  
This is the Privacy and Security Statement for I Want a New Girlfriend ([http://www.iwantanewgirlfriend.com](http://www.iwantanewgirlfriend.com/)).

This Privacy and Security Statement ("Privacy Statement") applies to information collected by I Want a New Girlfriend.  I Want a New Girlfriend is committed to protecting the privacy of its users ("Users") including visitors and members of the I Want a New Girlfriend web site.  We have created the following Privacy Statement to give you an overview of the type of information we collect, how the information is used, and how the information is safeguarded.

  1. WHO COLLECTS INFORMATION WITHIN THE SITE?

  Information is collected from Users on the I Want a New Girlfriend website.   The use of such information by I Want a New Girlfriend is governed by our own policies, practices, and procedures.  I Want a New Girlfriend may engage in selective sponsorship relationships with advertising companies, private individuals, and other Internet websites ("Sponsors").  Sponsors may or may not pay to have links, web site addresses, and / or their logo included on the  I Want a New Girlfriend web site and have it viewed by website Users.  Sponsors do not receive any personally identifiable information about Users directly from I Want a New Girlfriend. 

  2. WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED?

  In order to provide you with certain services throughout the I Want a New Girlfriend web site, information is collected in a variety of ways.  In some instances, I Want a New Girlfriend will ask Users directly for information in order for them to use certain web site services.  In other instances, information will automatically be collected as Users are using the website services.  The following is a summary of the type of information that I Want a New Girlfriend collects:

    1. Active Collection

  At several locations throughout I Want a New Girlfriend web site, certain information will be collected that you actively provide either voluntarily or as required in order to register with us.  The type of information may include the following:

      1. Contact information, such as name, mailing address, e-mail address and phone number. 
      2. Demographic information, such as age, gender, and zip code. 
      3. Information you enter in forms, optional surveys, our guest book, or contests.
      4. Information provided in connection with discussions boards, the Ask Donald section, and in messaging or other interactive services. 
      5. Information provided in email requests and communications. 
      6. Shipping or transaction information, such as billing address and credit card information, if you choose to purchase goods or fee-based services from the I Want a New Girlfriend store.   
 
    2. Passive Collection

  Some information is collected automatically while you are using I Want a New Girlfriend Web site.  It is important to note that I Want a New Girlfriend must store this information in order to ensure that its Users receive optimal service while using its services.  This type of information may include the following: 

      1. Log Files: Log files information, such as IP addresses, browser type, domain names, number of page views, login frequency, page or section accesses.  Log files are used to track member usage and engagement and to assess the effectiveness of our different services.  We also use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server.
      2. Cookies:  I Want a New Girlfriend may use cookies, which are electronic pieces of information used to keep track of information such as login name/passwords.  Some of our potential business sponsors may also use cookies.  However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. Cookies are used to: 
        1. Store session state information
        2. Authenticate Users 
        3. Help customize content delivery
        4. Provide context-sensitive help
        5. Collect information on the origin of User registration 
        6. Protect Web site security and login time-outs   
 
  3. WHY DO WE COLLECT CERTAIN INFORMATION?

  The reason why we collect certain information depends on the type of  service a person is using.  Most of the information collected from Users is voluntary in nature (i.e. registering as a member of I Want a New Girlfriend, signing our guest book, leaving information on a discussion board, etc.) and is used in order to create a User account on I Want a New Girlfriend and to validate User credentials while browsing I Want a New Girlfriend.  Other voluntary information is collected in order to provide content for the I Want a New Girlfriend website (i.e. postings to the I Want a New Girlfriend discussion board, Ask Donald questions, and more).

  4. HOW DOES I WANT A NEW GIRLFRIEND USE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED?

  I Want a New Girlfriend may use the information you provide in the following ways:

    1. For marketing and promotional purposes.  For example, to help understand the needs and interests of our Web site audience, I Want a New Girlfriend may use marketing data about its users.  
 
    2. To respond to your comments or requests or to request your feedback regarding our website, products, or services.  
 
    3. For billing purposes, to facilitate transactions and to fill a User's order in connection with purchases of goods or fee-based services offered by I Want a New Girlfriend.  
 
  5. WHAT INFORMATION IS SHARED WITH THIRD PARTIES?   

    1. I Want a New Girlfriend may disclose information you provide to us to independent contractors, service providers and consultants who assist us in our business or in providing Users with goods or services.  Such services providers may include, without limitation, credit card processing and shipping companies.  However, we will only share such personally identifiable information, as we deem necessary for them to carry out their obligations to I Want a New Girlfriend.  We may also share aggregated demographic information with independent contractors, service providers, consultants, advertisers and other partners.  Aggregated demographic information provided is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.  No information relating to online communications pertaining to specific issues of an individual or identifiable health information is shared with third parties.  
 
    2. I Want a New Girlfriend may also disclose personal information it has collected if necessary to fulfill our service obligations or if we are required to do so by law or if in our good faith judgment, such action is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process, to respond to any claims, or protect the rights of I Want a New Girlfriend and its Members and the public.  
 
  6. SECURITY

  The following outlines different types of security procedures I Want a New Girlfriend has implemented to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of the information collected.

    1. Identification and Authentication

We verify the identity of the persons accessing the data by using a login name and password chosen by the User upon registration. 

    2. Authorization and Access Control

 Only authorized people (e.g. I Want a New Girlfriend Administrators and the Database Administrator at [LoudOffice.com](http://www.loudoffice.com/)) have access to individually identifiable information data provided by Users.  Access to this sensitive data is revoked in a timely manner for any authorized person who changes function on I Want a New Girlfriend.

    3. Data Integrity and Retention

  We implement full database backups by our Database Administrator to establish data consistency and integrity.  We also grant Users access to their information in order to verify that the data is still accurate and has not been modified or corrupted.

  7. LINKING

  I Want a New Girlfriend Web site may offer links to other web sites.  Please be aware that I Want a New Girlfriend is not responsible for the privacy practices of such linked sites, including sites of our partners and advertisers.  We encourage our users to be aware when they leave the I Want a New Girlfriend web site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by I Want a New Girlfriend.

  8. CHOICE/OPT OUT

  I Want a New Girlfriend Web site has a feature that allows Users the ability to opt-out of receiving future communications by replying to unsubscribe via email to I Want a New Girlfriend.

  9. NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES

  I Want a New Girlfriend reserves the right to make changes to the Privacy Statement at any time.  If we plan to make significant changes to any of our privacy policies or practices with respect to how we use personally identifiable information, we will post those changes to this Web site 30 days before they take effect.  I Want a New Girlfriend will post those changes on its Web site so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  Please review our Privacy Statement periodically to see recent changes.

  10. ADDRESSING PRIVACY & SECURITY CONCERNS

  If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, including the practices or your dealings with I Want a New Girlfriend Web site, please contact us:

  I Want a New Girlfriend  
E-mail: [site@iwantanewgirlfriend.com](mailto:site@iwantanewgirlfriend.com).
